<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModEntry xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" Name="Zeta (IH Add-on)" Version="9" Author="ZipfsLaw" Website="https://www.nexusmods.com/metalgearsolidvtpp/mods/1309">
  <MGSVersion Version="1.0.15.3" />
  <SBVersion Version="0.0.0.0" />
  <Description>-=Features=-
• Mod Manager: Configure all of your mods in-game! You can toggle them, change their settings as well as their load order.
• Modding Framework: Using several new LUA functions, you can easily make the modifications you want without overwriting game files.
• Mod Support: Playable characters, vehicles, buddies, soldiers, missions, weapons, items, camos, LUA mods, and more!
• Non-Replacer Mods: Mods no longer conflict with one another! They can have their own unique assets without replacing vanilla content.
• Backwards Compatibility: Non-IH mods can be loaded by Zeta and used alongside other mods.
• Included Mods: Advanced Graphics Menu, Unlocked Weapon Customization, Zeta Editor

-=Disclaimer=-
Use Zeta at your own risk! 
All updates and releases are still mostly untested!
It is highly recommended to back up game saves and files!
Please report any issues, bugs, and crashes!
﻿
-=Requirements=-
• A legitimate copy of Metal Gear Solid V: The Phantom Pain,
Snakebite﻿
• Infinite Heaven﻿
• IHHook﻿
• Zeta Mods

-=Usage=-
•Download and install MGSV mods that require Zeta.﻿
•Hold down the Dive button (Space Bar) or press F3 to access the IH overlay menu.
•Scroll down to "Zeta Menu"
•To select an option, press right, or numpad 6.
•General Settings has options that change how Zeta works overall.
•Mod Management has options for all mods installed.

-=Special Thanks=-
401kPlan, BlackRock1207, blejky, BobDoleOwnsU, Buns, CapLagRobin, Chelly, Cuba, Daften_23, E2 Parajumper, Evergreen, ExplosiveResult, Glecas, Halfway Lambda, JimLaFluer, Jinmarr, Joey, Laughing Wallaby, Mare's Leg, Muffins, OldBoss, Ruda, Sai, Soda, Shigu, thatlegend101, Tinmantex, Unknown321, VenomRaven0, Ventos, YoungSn0w. 

And to Modders' Heaven for all the support!</Description>
  <QarEntries />
  <FpkEntries />
  <FileEntries />
  <WmvEntries />
</ModEntry>